...microphone working yes.
So, how everybody I know the...big and audience not that big so if you guys
...come closer?
Organized...to...to see each other my name is
yusef here steven who going to give you a talk about
how to effectively manage the network to meet the needs of your application so as,
you know, we have introduce something called the measure resource make
...infrastructure for as
...which you can describe through templates what they
...are in terms of the resources and
hardware composed and in the system will...for you today's talk is about how you can
describe the needs of view of the apps with respect to network how
...should look like how structured and how you can change it either imperative re also
a template basically okay so I'll give you a bit of setup of
...the basic model what you can do for the network on the like and why with
...developer and then see will come up and show you
the object model the restful api is
...the dishonor in their csharp portion how...can actually use the model?
Reminder please do submit evaluation please?
So, quick agenda will not...on this much tell you a bit more why would
...a value proposition for you why would you...developer to be able to control the network.
Give you a very quick view what about arm which is a as
a resource manager the way you which you describe that you replication and the way
the system orchestrate...and effectively is lifecycle management.
We'll tell you...more about...specific topic
for today which is the network resource provider which is the resource manager
...api in question here then we're going to go
through hands-on api assure demos cheer code.
And, we're...in the...your questions as well.
So, why should you care I mean we're here
...build...the reason for this talk if you remember anything here we want to
empower developers to control their own destiny?
To write the code quickly and to configured environment for the code quickly.
This could be in a...cycle or even production.
So, as, you know,...alright what I services...develops model we
...we tested we deploy it we monitored and we
fix it...something goes wrong or repeat in effect, effect we are solve removing other folks who
lisa depend on...applications done.
We have tooling.
And, now we also have a way for you to define the network of your application in all
...days you meaning how be able to
...some code testament aside but if you want something real.
...talked to somebody get your network manage
the network configured load balance, you know, the story.
With this system now everything is virtual...everything's software
...not only can you write the...your application but you can also
configured the network to replications needs or...software basically.
Lesley I want to emphasize that the in the plumbing underneath the cover
...for networking which can be quite extensive you don't have to do or
know everything about.
You can write application with the...as you're
in a very simple network flat network what every virtual machine for every into
talk to each other very simple crichton application that requires...a simple
load balance or as you will see in the gory details of the model
...can go down to defining networks a subbed that's and tackles and some stuff
frankly you only need to for very sophisticated applications so again
splice spectrum here disappears eagle.
Enables you to have a
...the ops model where you are in control your destiny.
You can write the...quickly and you can deployed quickly and you can change it
and environment around quickly to effectively software.
No, hardware needed here and no...
Heavy expertise rookies needed to get your applications the done.
So, we have discussed before the agile resource manager.
At the highest level...the very top you have the service...api is...effectively
every resources manager has something called a resource provider
and entity that export a bunch of api is.
And, what's...
It could be an ip.
Address for your network could be load better in point it could be virtual machine.
Could be a storage table, for example, these...resources
...basically is a way to uniformly describe?
In through templates and imperative api is how you can compose application
opted resources how they relate to each other and how should they be deployed
cohesiveness does orchestration for you for your resources?
And, you
...effectively every resources badger the exports through
our through the same uniform fashion and the constituted
the for networking effectively apply...resource providers.
The restful api is the language bindings over them so forth.
So, the consistency is important and
the flexibility is very important and note gets to arm you'd
be will find templates we get a publish...
those templates a template described...the topology of the application or
...resources that you need to make the application to actually come to existence you can start with
an existing template modify to your needs
...me have some of the gory details that you can forget or
become modify...so within this
model we can also do the same now for once...of resources are the network resources.
One more thing...before...networking per say once you buy into
our model you get a bunch of benefits that accrue to all resources
...adj I mention the grouping function moments...so
you can manage collection of diverse resources basically has units.
...template with say this how the...other this how they should be configured when you
...one configured that one so forth so does a groupie function.
And, you end up with ecosystem interface the same architecture will apply both and...the public
klout and on premises as...and the other talks here in other forms
...show you how effective the same model the same concepts apply to interface.
You also have ...of we end up with features
...come in for all resource providers,
for example, are back broad-base x control what he can
dissed described for each resource who can do what do it who can
modify token just monitored so forth you get tagging resources we can
at attach tags to resource...that way?
And, of course has with other resources and as you can decide in which
...or location they have to live.
On the your...
They are really three core resource providers that are very close to each other and which showed object
modern how...to each other the second is a compute resource provider which
describes applications basically virtual machines so
forth distortions source provider...storage dependencies of the application and this
would now there is a network resource...which describes the network topology of your
application and things like load balancing in points
aac olsen subnet...as I mentioned more details and perhaps...beginning?
...they are the...between these and you can put them in a very much
...declarative model...these templates you see examples as what...
In addition to be able to describe them to our declarative model...template
you-can comparatively manipulator resources at the very bottom like
everything else and arm these are restful...api is the
...rest resources were restful...against them.
And, we have csharp bindings we have java bindings
we have our shows...which can manipulate this...guys.
Now I give you
...the high-level...resources are haiti page other so forth and how you can do it with
a network let's talk about this is one slide?
Very quick solve the what features you can do to
...network in asher.
And, this light predates the are model by the way so I tore the existence but simplistic
...apps live in virtual networks optima cloud somewhere.
You decide the location and a virtual network think of it...an envelope
...your app just talk and talk to each...
As...everybody else's is isolation boundary if you...if you want to into the
does session boundary you have to effectively have...ip addresses which can
goal and...inter the applications and those ip addresses can do also
thinks he can be load balanced you can put to access control list on them.
You can do global load balancing through dns
base system.
We...to the internet come through our infrastructure which or
...protection so forth so you have virtual network up in the cloud your app runs in
there and you can.
Preacher application through public ip addresses...sophisticates.
You can do a lot by the way within the virtual network
...can if you applications sophisticated that you
...subnet teeing or multiple...or frontier talk...can do so...between them.
the template...mentioning earlier the on-base templates can...topology in a declarative.
How can have a library of these so...you don't have to start from scratch?
In addition by the way you can connect to your this advance now if you can
connect your resource in the klout through backing connectivity either through
vp and services and...are services they are scenarios for that offer
truly advanced scenarios you can go through private connectivity.
Which you can use a service from...called express
...to connect your customers all premises the cloud that's a bit too much perhaps
for today but the point is everything behind me here can
be now manipulated through software?
Through, through the representation fc behind me here can be declared in a simple template where you
...have to worry about much of complexity all the way down
although down to declaring and managing subnet...details as well.
And, leslie...you basic templates to get to
oper running and then as you get more sophisticated applications that they can go
define more details.
So, the whole the rest of the talk is what api is what
formats to use to actually you
...distinct for the needs of your application.
So, using the network...provider which fits the basic our model.
You can wire application as
...the network to meet applications you can do things like,
for example, have simple bunch of e m running levine at?
Media with the public ip address that.
Already can say I whenever load balance or...virtual.
That balances through, through some policy a bunch of e m all down the all the way down to
heavy multitude applications what ankles so forth.
And, I keep...I mentioned all the properties have mentioned earlier
...being the declarative so forth applies to hit as well.
Ok, let's...some details now.
He's a basic object model and this is simplified version of it of the
objects resources if you are in our model here.
And, there are...relationship between the storage site
...but look at the to decipher a second the basic concept is
in the right-hand side you see the virtual network.
This is the resource in which are applications
on-base basically and you can have
...within.
The virtual network if you want to
...segmented depending replication needs.
If security's a very high priority within your applications set you can apply something called the...
security group and to show examples of this what you can apply policies
...submits tackles on the submits order ibm's even.
You can declare load balances which you
can have public ip addresses that are load balance among a bunch of lms.
And, you could go down even lower if you want to have the notional over network interface
...multiple them to privy m their scenarios like that this one...more details as one.
Okay,...come over...even will now go through next level
of detail here we'll talk about the object models in some detail and which would exactly as
...thank you?
So, unfortunate nobody laptops giveaway today but this it's very interesting so we
start working...the optimal reps and here is...model for
to new core or...within arm those of you are familiar with the
current service much interface for as your...no that we've got
to general flavors we have paths and we have ios and for paths if you want to create below
...for example,...you get automatically when you create a
pass cloud service you create the cloud service you get your
gm's you get your lower bouncer you get your public ip...package.
With ios there's a little bit more control you get your gm's you get
...groups and you get a cloud service still ...can specify that dns on the
cloud service what that doesn't really allowed to do very well is to
decompose that and only create what you want great.
So, with this with this new model
we decomposed all of these relationships into a
...modular framework so here
we're representing storage computer network also
...ecosystem not represented here are like websites the sequel
leisure a and various others in the growing ecosystem of resource providers all
which have interdependencies all of which are modular
all of which allow you to create the applications institutions where you want to create.
Which is also ...dimension...for to...submits and
...bouncers...likes as...the same...bones
...can be made internal by just having no public ip or
...becomes...external low-pass come to public low bouncer does no change to
lower bound to itself all of this is used on the
...front-end side of low bouncer so
...you're testing something then you have your application there you have your preempts ready
lower bound to running your validating internally and then you were to go live with it
...a public ip exposed the internet...some network security groups to as network
tackles accident access control lists and then you're going to
go course person hit that endpoint straight away so,
it doesn't require new deployment doesn't require any huge musc
...works scope on the compute
...this briefly the virtual machines they'll have a extensions so you
can have extensions...to create papon jeff and
...extensions so these were wrong when the
pm is created so it's not just about getting a...orf virtual
...with nothing on it you can complete your solutions you can have your deployments
...into your vm into new
...using papon chef so on to get
your application get to configure to build it so that you can model your
complete end-to-end application so...low-power here...we've taken some water?
Ok, so, in terms of mouth interfaces
d formation of everything we're doing here is to rest api all of your
...implement vest api
...use json for request responses rest semantics and,
everything else is built on top of that we have x
...we have our show that talk directly to diversity api
...essentially and then we have the adverse st case we've got no
gs dot net sdk job sdk others there's like as
your has a commitment to other communities such as.
Python will be and remember...them but...and...burp
...implementing the support for these new or
...in all of
this so it's going to be whichever way you want to manage we've got to cover.
Okay,
so, did...a...more detail of take one example
of one through a few examples of how we use
this rather than look at everything and try to
...to a very...level...discotheque...very deep?
So, what I'm looking at here is network
...groups as you mention in the last couple of slides network steered
group...software firewall allowing you to
configure articles the access control lists within your
virtual networks to allow or disallow traffic great?
The demonstrate group is de-couple from network security rules so you can
of individual rules to allow
...traffic point if any of you version firewall
...four-wheel you're used to describe interface withhaving policies
in applied in priority order to...allow or restrict
...which great the.
Properties of these...but...properties here for the
obscured rule are the ones you expect they are...going through this
...detail because you can be used...over and over again and I'm sure that...ordering.
So,...for rule our protocol tcp udp source
short-range destination port range...as a visit weepy is
that sh is that whatever address and destination prefix is
deacon specified source traffic destination traffic...for example,
you can black hole countries and say
dot to develop a or you can open up to individual people individual
...and say I want that person to be able to...to use my service on the
upward...our tonight priority is...sit in the rules
...and then direction is whether inbound or...
Now we have that.
So, looking at how we do this rest.
So, up here...
Let me zoom...
The thing that's.
Udp so...that top of this screen.
We have the method dogma port here with rest of this put
post we support...to...for each object it is item
...it can be overridden if you
wish by the use of header which is if match?
And, I thought works with the tags to allow you...use
it in either create or update...for.
Don't care it works neither?
So, look, at url we see that everything is stop-off.
Https management...dot com subscriptions
your so by the resource groups which we saw in the
...earlier these are containers that we used to manage resources within the our model.
And, then we have the namespaces which mix of
the network and then we talking about the next...groups.
Here and it was...name and then
diversion work of the...using right.
So, if we look at the request we see is...it's.
Simple...easy-to-understand there's a defined
schema for this so you can validated quite easily
the parameters are pretty much as you'd expect all down here of
...using their for allowing sh.
The...protocol...tcp udp port ranges
...destination port range because...document
inbound rule that means anybody from the internet commune deport is...but this rule.
And, then on the destinations...on response side
...back after we send...over...server.
We see a couple things one the...is known in the payload
of response because this object exists this object now has
a unique yuri and yuri is this will appear management
...calm blah-blah-blah until
...and...tag allows us to use to do
concurrent control convert access to this resource sowe want to update
...we specified...tag in the if match header and then we
if it doesn't matter exactly request fails so that symbiosis modifying the same resources same time.
And,...we have this dirigibles down here...
...the...rules...a
...collection of the...we created.
It's the exact same with specified with one addition which is the
...appear which is unique your...for this obscurity rule within the...
Also the bottom we have default security rules and this is
...mentioned because this wasn't
in the request this is added automatically as the default property of
...security rules about the security group is secure
by default so when you apply this your subnet when you apply to your network interface card
...prevents traffic coming in from the internet unless you explicitly
...so this goes to...any concerns you might have about having
...test environment creature security group apply to your subnet
your secure unless you open it up does not traffic getting in there.
...so, I'll.
Move the next one
...see the exact same thing but csharp.
And, here musing museum-an here I'm using the
I'm...I'm doing this here is that I'm getting a authentication token
I'm adding a token cloud credential down-and-out here's work it's interesting.
Microsoft as your dot network.
The...as your management of network dot resource provider client applied
Very long...
But, this is the dot sdk...can use to manage my.
...network resource...
...exactly added expect
...create a new security rule by itself and the adding
a twenty-fifth moment specify all the same properties all happy.
...then down here.
I create a new security group ...location here.
And, a new list of security...and,
district rule toward...does not security...
And, then I possible over to the entropy client and saying creek this erp
data or whatever and it was...that as...take for my operation.
So, I think this the dev here is resource group description wonder
...sg is the name of the and...security rules I want to create.
...or update.
And, no, current the next one we see partial is actually think I'm not good well in
...example but now so,
over...this side we have museum-an excuse me.
Ok, over this...have a partial
...great new measure network security will conflict we have all the same farms we have
...there and what is creating an object in memory here is does not I should persist can
you can to the to serbia?
And, then underneath we have...network security group.
Specified resource group namely...in location and then pass in this
object as a ...say...group have these rules.
...the output side which is kind of interesting.
Ok, the name of the network...group creative great the location
...unique identifier this is the big long management
...so on this can be used in for the rotates
...in the dependencies laptop will about them later
each tags and schedules and here we notice that this is jason.
So, other saying earlier everything about the interfaces you're going to use to
talk to arm is about rest ...you can talk you can do with
...can do with ...case underneath the organ translate over to json.
Okay, and, then at the end
receivable of references their this dimension the default security rules mention that network
interface and submits these are any network interfaces...so that's the
...to use this particular group and we have not yet sort of like.
Versed operations...are supported again just using this example.
For network,
network security groups we support creating rotating throughput.
...getting through get obviously listings work as
...and then deleting through delete
the relative urls these all relative to the management of measure...
these are for...we leave a blank slate we put...and
...name into the ...were posting to for putting to...and for
...the same thing for listing reliever blank we just get all that security
represent...we can filter and...of contour or get that collection and,
then deleting as...as well predictably then jason request response for
...we don't...anything forgetting or listing is only
...and then we get...response ...at least we have no
...looking...in the body and then we got status...like two hundred four hundred
four depending...whether the object plus deleted or what are the object
was that can be found didn't exist in...
And, then just briefly touch on this which is that the bottom of the table here
...groups is an object or resource that contains network security
rules so how about semantic works with
in the arm framework is that when using these verbs.
To access charles resources essentially then we just append the name of charger
title charles security rules...to create or update get.
Or listthat gives all obscured
...we have configured for this network security ...
that's...so predictable what...completeness make sure us there.
Okay, so.
A number of items are provided ...wide as use...for.
...resource porters...better arm one of the things that's implemented
...so this is an example of how we can use this
feature that's...to get audit logs from
a particular scope and scope we have here is a network
security group so then we go off and say well
who's modify this security group who's...leader to use whatever and,
this allows them to get the detail similar functionality is
there for back attacking as well...the same
are provided structure we can specify that we have.
...back is we can specify that certain user
groups have access to certain resources for certain paths.
Uncertain...dot so that if you wanted to
...yourself make sure nobody else messed with it or whatever then or back is way to
templates template...do we just right now so please...zoom into little bits in
a second templates are realism templates are allow you
to specify multiple resources in one file with dependencies
which support for parameters which support for variables
which support for looping within the...so, for example,
you can have one temple file which was a totally but, the...one
...file that will have your virtual network your submits...group all the
things talked about plus...bouncer svm.
Virtual machine extensions that would deploy replication
injure ibm's and also.
Public ip to expose that ...bouncer to the public and how all the
...between them and all dependencies that-you might have between
...website and them as well?
So, the critical things to look at here.
That is what is jason point define schema.
Then we have parameters variables and resources parameters
are user provided we have support for the...we support for
input masking in terms of rejects so on native types as well.
...resources, resources are as you said collection of.
Resources from across to resource voters not to talk...networking
the other interesting things we have...here to have any yes here's what we
see depends on that's interesting so we have a network interface
we're saying well this depends on the virtual network so...network.
Therefore conceptually must be created before grated for network within the
virtual network these are...arm...so
it can deconstruct...template into a dependency...and then.
...those requests to various resource providers to make sure that
...don't get ahead of ourselves and try to instantiate something we can't just entry yet because the
parent doesn't exist or depends...exist and suited to maximize efficiency so we
...maximum throughput minimum timex student...
and all the parallelization...but the arm level as opposed to you
...to figure out what's the best most often way to do-it-yourself which is...
Okay, so.
We have lots of things that are...spend too much time
...this because we're going to go through a bigger example in a second but just
to call your attention down on the partial to use this template is
...do we have partial
...resource group we also have support to do...an expert so on and,
specified name typify we want to use.
What reading want to depose into...then the name parameters that we want to
...dimension one quick thing and that is.
How you create amplifies...to one template for here and it's got...
to networks and submits and security groups...virtual things and?
That might be find might be to purposes fine both you might want to separate out and
...want to keep
...my dmv...one template I...to have might back-end a separate...so,
you don't have like a single files that are really big...very difficult to see what's going on and,
you can put all of them the same resource group you can then manage those particular
layers of...us as atomic...by...updating
...readability applying to template and then the goes tickets reset
...for of resources contained within...template but,
if you specify something in a template.
Sometime later you
removed from the template doesn't get over it it's still there.
So, it tempt doesn't precept the whole thing...we set the whole
...only reset what knows about what
you specifying template so-if you you're not going to accidentally wipe out
...resources by applying a template to resource group.
Okay,I think
...pretty talked enough about the powerpoint so that's a look at thissome of the connection.
...better.
So, switching over so you can see...doing...
...so, here we have a template.
So, we have...same construction result second ago
we have parameters variables resources...by the way is to small...okay.
And, we have types we have names locations we
...so indus
...I'm trying to create a virtual network
that security group submits ...bouncer couple of e m
...public ip underflow bouncer some of the
...some interesting things on the network level down...the end.
So, look, at expend that the...bouncer...here.
We see a lot of things here for low bouncers
we see front-end ip can fix we see back-end address pools...the
...blow bouncing rules probes and in by not rules so this really very configured
...bouncer that allows us to control the traffic as it goes through ...back-end
an interesting thing as well is this...rules.
This allows you to specify tunnels basically through your.
Low bouncer using pork address translation to have
...outside pork that thing...here, for example, apes uses in
...to for traffic ...dp three nine into a particular
...back-end all the ways of doing the same thing will be to have a
virtual network...vp end on your virtual network so that you can
access everything privately or having a public ip directly on your via
...don't have to do...that...the...bouncer?
one other thing dented...attention to here is dependencies so this
low bouncers dependent virtual network that's also depend on photocopy.
Okay, so, what I want to do here we have
a template so that's just have look and see if we can get deployed?
Excuse me okay.
So, here I have.
A our shell.
The most make sure that just doesn't exist fine.
And, I have all the parameters required to ruled this.
Template
unscripted password for the p it's random and,
then specifying the resource group name I want to use...is sample out dev
...follow want use as well...description idname prefix of this
from this to make sure that...have to repeat the same thing over and over again using variables in the
...to than...the names of all the resource I want to use so that
...all prefix...us hyphen dev hyphen bm...for example.
And, storage count name...pretty...be stored...the public ip address
name...interesting we look at...second and then the have been...password that...
So, where is my course about machine?
Ok, so, let's just run this see what happens.
But, you so.
Here we see vested create this application
...excepted template sense valid great ones do now is it's breaking down
...for the resources...is figure
...best way to do this is then going to go off to...or...as
...with as much parallelization as a can so that it's not just about well,
these are network these compute these storage and encoding this and this and parallel
saying well okay look at to the answer I would call that in parallel
...the compute resource provider twice and parallels to create my to
...in parallel instead of having to do...then
...the other one so on which could quickly and easily get very onerous and the point of view
...environment so that's all running
...seeing a lot of success here all these things are fine.
...there.
Now I want to switch over...before go-there believe this...
And, switch back to top again switch back to the...
Templates are great the reactor...both
to love text and, a lot of different resources on different schemas so on.
This could be...problem but from...challenge from the
point managing point of view been creating these initially and,
then the editing as you go up.
We already saw the our
...response was...and we'll see
later that the objects are jason as well everything
...so there's nothing to stop you going in creating
your objects using a...partial or.
Or done sdk and then using the...you get back in those
questions to create...a different way.
...is to use can templates we've created...
Thanks-giving is template canned tempest we've created this command
will go to...
The as your resource manager template library and will list out the
...we've created in this library that you can use and they range from
sequel leisure to processing their websites networking
and very sort of things to give you a headstart into
...applications to...you what creative?
And, let me just to open...one of these...action.
Excuse me...
This will just take one second apologies.
Okay,...first commando...executed there is to switch
...as your mode of the partial...and...which is the our
Using the.
The service...api...using now to.
The...temps as well...
Okay.
There.
So, what's doing that's.
Going to go back here I want to show you these templates.
So,...segment subscription and then show you the campus of air.
So, over the left-hand side.
Should then stressing list so love temperature already user there to give you
headstart on the on your application templates and in addition to
that is also quite large library of template available?
These are created by either microsoft internal
a and, vp and we expect this to grow quite rapidly as people start creating
templates the cover different scenarios we have templates you're ready for
obvious pre-law bouncers but also creating your v m with papon jeff and,
all these little things opted to install things after the image creative.
Saucepan so switching back then to
...point we have going so we've got this going already
...for...both of them and earlier so,
I'm going to show you what looks like.
I've created one of these already earlier on today and it's for
a stage application is the same template it's got the same.
Resources all of the...change parameters so, here we have virtual machines.
...showed...what to virtual machines
...w what hyphen stage...and vm they one of the able...
here we have the full jason...we have.
Variability...belongs to the storage profile...phd these
and we have the network profile which is network interface.
As we saw earlier with the object model network interfaces no,
longer automatically created as part of the virtual network...you can manager separate
...move network interface to different bm noob.
...then we have.
The other one which is the same disco different a looping is
a is a way of within templates haven't
on this position example puts away free to create multiple objects at the same
...variances just...name so you have like...to...mthree so looping is
...you that and you can...for example,...fifty...in
your lobe onset in the space of a few minutes...then we have the microsoft's
networks names base with all the objects in here.
Visual great.
So, in here we have network security group.
And, we have never...with no security holes so
we seen earlier that network security group no security rules will.
Block everything however,...stage environment and them kind of thinking that I want to open up
to state environment to...
To let them have local and...so if I switch back to here.
Excuse me.
Well, actually that's all finished that's awesome so the template we run who started when
...install this...environment is there...preempt...bouncer the
...of staff which is pretty awesome
...looking at ti.
Looking at the stage environment we created earlier.
I want to have a look at the public ip because I
won't be able to give this public ip to a customer and have them
or dp into this into one of these...tableau...doing?
And, I see.
That are specified...school over I've specified...main
...here as entropy website stage...
Arm then translate this network
...than translate this into this dns
...entropy website stage...deployed in the...
Dns optional on
this using here for convenience you don't have to use dns of public herpes
...you can use the ip and, we don't.
Fourth-grade reverse...dn is interest
...as well public...support the creation of
...your records to a label you toast male servers and things like that might require
a peter service of your records.
So, of copy that so I want to have a look and see
...is...open is three nine open so
...using a tool here that is the tooling this develop interning microsoft
...basically those ping using tcp it makes a connection and then twice
connecting udp port very similar
...tool both I didn't want to get ping to work from here look, so,
we...and destination name important...hit is three nine.
...we'll go with that.
...that's a problem.
So, I won't give this a customer but...connector.
So,...do about this look at the thing...great earlier
okay no security rules...security...so everything we
look at so far in terms of templates has been declarative.
...resources we model the dependencies we've scented
...arm of create everything all the
...of which is also...sometimes you want to do imperative
as well sometimes you want to all this stuff is great...to do
...digital thing and that's where you can...comparatively you
don't have to use declarative you can do everything comparatively if you want to or you can do everything declarative and
never...imperative...whichever way you want to do it whatever works view.
I've got a visual studio application and,
I'm going to go and creek that's...rule that
...missing to allow three eight nine inbound to allow me to connect
all the what I'm doing that I'm going to...
...discriminant this is constantly probing
...point twenty connect twenty connect...connect so all going well when
I actually discovered this was...so...looking...field.
...so, that's what...looked a bit of this I'm
...make this little bit bigger so we can see it same...looked at a
couple seconds go on the csharp slide where instantiating
...the algebra network client
...to execute this...doing some different here we're not creating
rotating you were getting some that's already there surpassing in the resource
...passing in the object I want to manage which is
the ws stage industry is the name of
...getting the name updated resource group...the...security group I want to
...so let's.
Start with...
...to this.
The authentication model amusing force me to do this so.
...a second.
Step over this.
Didn't...good?
...I've got to come up with this to...
So, now we retrieved...group
...collection is the object that we created by...of
...the containing the execute group...rules.
Rules are...so, we need to rectify that...over this.
Creating new security rule same structure we saw before we
We have for all these
properties set specified normally fine specifying portrays...
The between...three-ninety stepping over this ...adding a to collection of rules
...group...
And, mobile truth we're going to put this back and server we're going to put this back to...
...second.
Okay, ...response...okay.
...worked.
...then we stepped into the...to return true...
What effect...here we expect to see that of a switch back to
the...resource explore sorry didn't introduce this is
a preview to that allows you to like look, at all your resources
...for creating ...it's phasing so on it allows you to
...of...here you can create new ones through the
actions you-can delete them and you can experiment with your...you-can
...resources...use this as a have very handy helper for create your own
...creating object creating resource going here looking to json copy of your
template?
Gotten there so I go here...refresh this.
One expectancy history role.
Okay,...go back.
Didn't like that?
So, expand this one...groups.
Not askew things in here stage stages when we did earlier
and we look at network and we look at security groups.
There...awesome we switch back here
he is the command-line does been constantly
pinging this endpoint and we see.
That as of.
Around mineral goal is connecting...working it's.
The rules been deployed the network firewalls essentially has been updated to do
...traffic...node to connect...I can give this my customer
...connect you can have a look that's all fine so that's all as we expect.
So, the switch back then to...
Okay.
We started with what...care about this and, just to recap.
We want you to liberate your development tested experiences by
enabling you to manage these resources and create these into...applications in a very lightweight
...way you can use the same interfaces to manage resources
in storage of networking computing websites at the same type of
interface reston jason is consistent across all of
these and delivers value ad such as all back...tagging so, on the
...sentry on the on the...platform enabling you to have a better experience.
...enables you very easily to have repeatable experiences
...repeatable deployments for your...test important...and
it's represents the best classroom structure existing interfaces fast versioning and
...course.
Basically allows you turner code into networks if you want in whichever ways
...working...code if you want to use.
Experts...if you want to use jobs sdk what use know the gs.
Solvent it's whatever works you and,
you can have this in your realtime...configured exactly as you want.
Without energy onerous process associate with those changes.
Okay, so, we're comical
one-time-only commits for questions so call-to-action there's a number
talks on today that are...of an expert data really also markus in
this talk is virtual for dislodged so you can obviously tent...I advise
you have look about if you-get-a-chance employed online then we have a
...seeming which is introduction what's new...a is I'll talk a
lot more about the compute side of the...resource...
...talk tomorrow with...in which ...some scale
...application...on friday...machines deep...
can be pretty cool talk ...compute...one of look at compute extensions so on
...compute ox are certainly worth checking out and
try to like as of today were public review so these are freely available to
...there's no sign of required to resources underneath our
ga resources so...will pay for resources...so you have microsoft
...to pay around and,
...of those credits for getting...with this.
Okay, so,...
But, the resources underneath our...network
...r ga but the resource provider these
...of a...public review today ...
amount interface sitting over these resources but resource themselves...
Loxels and,
take control your networks and do it as you want to do...couple of
...slides and resources there if you want to...microsoft measure?
...school.
And, then piece evaluate ...get better so any comments appreciated.
So, thank you...your time any questions.
Distribute
...feedback item more suggestion is to when we're using
declarative and templates when we create a bunch of objects and then we imperative
...delete something then potentially that changes then lost so ...
justin is that we somehow tractor change...impaired to change to template are
...server-side assume or somewhere and then give the option to replay those...changes
...happen to...template...at some point out that it's an interesting suggestion
...certainly...team unseen what makes sense?
Yes,...to follow author...of would be...
...everything which...what execute your imperative changes
model everything back then again to a template...and your source control and then
your source control that as most of data but not another...me go...pointy
...iterative model is much better...is useful if you control...
Yes, I agree.
Thank you very value feedback...else.
Okay, I can see anybody those kinds of okay,
well, thank you all your time was represented here have great build...laptops.